Love in Winterland is a tv movie, romance film directed by Pat Williams.
Ally, a final contestant on a dating show, must face her high school
sweetheart when she is chosen for the Hometown Date.
Ally, played by Italia Ricci.
Brett, played by Chad Michael Murray.
Tanner, played by Jack Turner.
Lauren Burns, played by Aliyah O'Brien.
Helene, played by Teagan Vincze.
Molly Wilson, played by Wanda Cannon.
Winterland, called at first New Dreamland Auditorium and later Winterland Arena and Winterland Ballroom, was an
ice-skating rink and music venue in San Francisco operational from 1928 to 1979 and demolished in 1986.
Built at the corner of Post Street and Steiner Street, it was converted for exclusive use for music
in 1971 by concert promoter Bill Graham, who made it a popular stop for rock acts.
Graham's related merchandising company Winterland Productions sold
concert shirts, memorabilia and sports-team merchandise.
The tone is emotional.